How do you balance the plan? Let's
talk about generational
wealth or paman plan, which I mentioned
earlier. How can I explain to you
the four generational plan? Here
you can understand how
the four generations will benefit from the same
plan. Let's say we have a grandfather
who took out a policy, he is the
policy owner and his grandson is the
insured. His son or simply the
father of his grandson made him a
contingent owner. Those are
our characters here in our paman plan. Remember,
we have a guaranteed cash value that
the policy owner will receive. The policy owner will
receive a guaranteed
cash benefit equal to 6% of the face
amount. Remember, in our example
earlier, 1 million was taken out of 30 million.
So let's say 1 million was also
taken by grandfather for his grandson. So on
the sixth year of the palac year, grandfather
will receive php6,000
annually. While
he is alive, if grandfather dies,
the ownership will automatically go
to his son or
his grandson's father, who was made a
contingent owner by grandfather, and because
he is a contingent owner,
The guaranteed cash benefit will automatically go to him
now, he will enjoy
receiving 60,000
yearly now if the father is gone,
the ownership of the policy
will automatically go to the insurer to the
grandson, so he will also receive 6%
of the face amount as long as
he lives, of course the grandson
or ours, our insured will be
old, he will also have a
wife, he will also have a love life,
and of course he will also have
his own child, wherein
his child can be made the beneficiary
because he is the policy owner, he is the
insured in this plan, his
beloved child will be the
beneficiary, so that at the time
he is gone, our guaranteed benefit
will automatically go to the grandson,
imagine just one policy and yet who are the ones who
enjoyed his policy,
grandfather, father, grandson, and then the grandson
to the grandson, so four generations will
enjoy this one policy.
So that's how we can make it a
legacy for our grandparents. So
if you think about it,  I don't have any
grandchildren yet, I'm just a child, so
of course we'll go into the
three Generation paman plan. In the three
Generation pamana plan, these are
our characters. Father,
Mother, and son this time. You who have a
child. Get a policy for your child.
You are the policy owner now. You made
your spouse a contingent owner. Of course, right? Of course,
if you lose your
wife or husband, he will be the automatic
owner of your child's policy.
Who will enjoy our
guaranteed cash benefit? Of course,
Father will enjoy it first because of course,
he is the policy owner. If
Father is gone, the ownership will go to the
mother and she will be the one
to receive our guaranteed cash
benefit. Of course, this child will
also grow up.
He will also have his own love life and
of course, they will have a new
product. At the time when
Mother is gone, the contingent owner again,
the ownership of the policy will automatically go to the child
and he will be the one to
receive the guaranteed cash benefit
when the insured is gone. Of course,
he designated his child, his
beloved child, as the beneficiary
and the  His son will receive the
guaranteed death benefit, so again, it's the same
plan, but three generations
enjoyed it: father, son, and grandson.
Even if father is gone,
he will still leave something behind so that his family won't be left behind.